# NATALIA SENTEMOVA

### **STACK**

 $\mathsf{React} \cdot \mathsf{Typescript} \cdot \mathsf{CSS} \cdot \mathsf{HTML} \cdot$ 

responsive design · Scss/Sass · Tailwind ·

styled-components · material-ui · RTK ·

Redux · MobX · Jest · Java · Node.js ·

MySQL · Webpack · Vite · eslint · prettier ·

Next.js · Docker · Storybook · FSD

### **PROJECTS**

### **SpiritMe**

https://studio.spiritme.tech/

## Personal page

https://talisent.github.io/resume/

### Drag & drop

https://talisent.github.io/todo-list/

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

★ Leetcode

Solved 50+ problems

# LANGUAGES

Russian	Native	•••••
English	Proficient	••••
Hebrew	Beginner	••••
German	Intermediate	••••

# Frontend Developer (React, TS)

+7-968-889-9087 @ ns.sent@yandex.ru

Phttps://talisent.github.io/resume/ Phttps://github.com/taliSent

Tel-Aviv, Israel 🌣 https://www.linkedin.com/in/natalya-sentemova/

### SUMMARY

A frontend developer with 3.5 years of experience with TS & React. Successfully finished more than 7 different projects, mostly in fintech. Worked in a team of specialists and as a sole developer. I create scalable and maintainable interfaces, that users love.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Frontend Developer

06/2023 - Present

SpiritMe

https://spiritme.tech/

Led the development of an Al-video creation startup.

- Implemented an advanced video editor and augmented it with features, crucial for Al video generation, creation of preview, .
- Introduced a draft system to save unfinished videos.
- Optimized the bundle, by reducing the initial page loading time 6-fold.
- Changed app's interface in 2 days to align it with the latest business demands.
- Integrated with the app aggregator to increase the number of users.
- Provided comprehensive code reviews.

## Frontend Developer

10/2019 - 01/2023

Cinimex

https://www.cinimex.ru/

Developed 7+ different applications, most of which were bank apps, each with unique business logic.

- Created an application, allowing users to configure, view and sign PDF documents.
- Engineered a Node.js & React app, that performed conditional redirects and error message management for a system of applications.
- Debugged and refactored a corporate social network.
- Developed a personal account for owners of a specific car model.
- Designed 10 pages of an app, that was used to create bank accounts for legal entities.
- Delivered 4 page-sized tables / forms, allowing users to manipulate the table data.

### QA / SQL Developer

05/2018 - 10/2019

### **AT Consulting**

Led the team of 3 QAs of the Central Bank application for global monitoring of taxes.

- Developed and tested Java & SQL widgets.
- Developed end supported E2E tests with Selenium & Java.
- · Created SQL testing data.
- Developed a large 30-paged generated pdf form, filled with 50 SQL queries, each with complex business logic.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of physics

2012 - 2016

**Moscow State University** 

React p. I, p. II
Code Academy

2021